If you have purchased a health plan, then
you will definitely need to know here
which hospital comes
under the network hospital, that is,
which hospital is providing you cashless facility on your pay.
If you have health
insurance of ICICI Lombard,
then I am going to explain it to you in detail. At
any specific location, at
any pin code, you
can find out in detail which hospital is there within this pin code by
typing it with them.
You can get complete information.
You
can get complete details on any state, on any city. So, please stay tuned to this
video till the end.
Then, by continuing the video, you will know my name.
And you are watching Tech Invented Simply, I will give
you a screenshot on the side,
please pay attention there.
First of all, you will need an application
which is going to be I will take care
application which is available on Google Play Store.
You can definitely open it after installing it from there.
I want to tell you
that you have to create an account here, that is,
if  If you have a system mobile number
available, then definitely you
can log in with the registered mobile number, you will get
to see the complete details, you will get
to see your health policy number, along with this you will
get to see the complete details of the people in whose name the help policy is,
from this application alone, you
can easily manage your entire insurance here, you can see the same insurance, along with this, for
how many days it is going to be valid, how
you have to buy the policy, how you have to
settle the claim, if you do not know
how you have to settle the claim,
how you have to submit your document for nimbusment,
definitely I have
made a dedicated video on that,
I have made two-three video parts for all of you, you will get the link of those videos
in the description, please do
check it out, so here
you will see, you will see just the tech option, at the
bottom
you have to tap on the network, then
after doing that we go to some
section like this, you will see here at the moment
But in my area, there is only one
hospital available, that is, there is only
one hospital available on my pin code, which is the
super hospital zero kilometer away, that is, the
next hospital on my pin code, it is very close to
my house, so
I can definitely visit it and get my
cashless treatment done, I will not have to pay even ₹1, even
if you have to, you
can definitely settle this matter by holding an investment conclave and get your refund, so
here you will see the option below,
just on the left side of the location
search, it is normal, you have to tap on it,
after tapping, you
can easily update the location here and confirm it, and
after confirming, you will get to see the complete list here,
but if you want to find out the hospital name
in any specific pin code area or
yours, you can type 'Find out current
affairs', select the search category and
enter your details, so
here I have selected the category,
pin code, so normal or  I
enter my pin code, as
you can see here, double on, double zero, double seven,
I have entered it here,
after entering it, I actually press it, here you
can see Sarthak Medical Center, this
pin code is also the only network hospital
available, if you want to select out another, then
you will have to enter it again in the same way, so it is
normal or I
enter another pin code, all these pin
codes here are of Delhi only, so
simple, I press search here again,
after doing it, you will see here
many Rose Hospitals have been
typed here, you
can see here Jeevan Jyoti Hospital,
Ruprani Mango Hospital, along with this, Bam
Gupta Hospital Private Limited, in this
way, many of
their network hospitals are available at this location in this pin code,
through which you want to know, if you want to
talk to them, then here you get the option of mobile
number, location and navigation,
you can
also get your details by typing it easily here, so
normally you have to find out in this way,
if you  You have to check out the
complete list of hospitals available
in which areas all over India under which names, you will be
able to check it out here, you will be able to see it by
clicking here for the listed hospital, so
simply you have to click here,
after doing this
you will see that you will get some information,
a PDF will be downloaded in your phone
and you will definitely be
able to check it out here, so in the same way
you have to check out according to your location,
which network hospital
is linked with ICICI Lombard, so if you liked the date of hope, do
not get it, if you got the information from God, then
please like this video, I will
subscribe to the channel so much, only
for all of you, such well
content keeps coming, specimen, till then
bye take care, thanks for watching,
thank you